# **Jamie Robertson**

Full stack developer

hello.jamie@protonmail.com +44 (0) 7881 820 789

Github profile github.com/JamieRobertson

in LinkedIn profle linkedin.com/in/jamie-r/

I currently work as a full stack developer for Kano Computing, developing applications and platforms to help teach programming skills to children.

Right now I'm working on front-end applications using Typescript, including stemplayer.com, a creative music platform and collaboration with Kanye West.

I have over six years of professional experience working with the Django framework for web development and the React JavaScript library.

#### **Professional experience:**

## Kano Computing

June 2021 – Present | Full-stack developer

- Development of stemplayer.com, a collaboration with Kanye West.
- Development of world.kano.me and associated *Edutech* web apps.

### Reason Studios (formerly Propellerhead Software)

March 2014 - June 2021 | Developer

- Design & development of reasonstudios.com.
- Analysis and user segmentation based on engagement and behaviour.
- Marketing automation development, using Salesforce APIs.
- Infrastructure development, using Vagrant and Ansible, then Docker.
- Development of internal analytics dashboards.

#### Monki

April 2013 - January 2014 | Graphic designer / Final art

- Design for a range of material for print and web.
- Development of online campaigns for monki website.
- Design & development of internal sites to be used by store employees.

## **Bright Young Things Tuition (consultant)**

September 2012 - March 2013 | Mobile app design / development Design & implementation of educational mobile apps.

#### **Craftsman Websites**

January 2012 - August 2012 | Design / development
Projects included the 'Notting Hill Carnival App' a cross platform mobile app.
Technologies used included PhoneGap and the Google maps API.

#### **Technology I have experience working with:**

**Python**: Django, Scrapy, Celery, Flask

JavaScript: Typescript, React, Reflux, Redux

**iOS**: Swift, React Native

**Design**: Sass, Photoshop, Illustrator, inDesign, Sketch, Figma **Infrastructure**: AWS, Docker, Vagrant, Ansible, Webpack

Databases: Django ORM, Postgresal, MongoDB

**Other:** *Salesforce*, *Adestra* 

## Technologies I have worked with in the past:

pHp, Wordpress, ActionScript (Flash), ColdFusion

#### **Education:**

Edinburgh College of Art - University of Edinburgh. Visual Communication Graduated 2010